Are you really going to retire, Miss Marsh?
Marsh小姐,您真的准备退休吗?
I may.
有可能.
I can't make up my mind.
我还拿不定主意.
I will have to ask my future husband.
我得问一下我的未婚夫.
He won't let me make another film.
他不会再让我拍电影了.
Your future husband, Miss Marsh?
您的未婚夫,Marsh小姐?
Yes. Let me introduce him to you.
是的,让我把他给你们介绍一下.
His name is Carlos.
他叫Carlos.
We're going to get married next week.
下星期我们就要结婚了.
Look, Liz!
看啊,Liz!
Here's another report about Karen Marsh.
这又有一篇关于Karen Marsh的报道.
Listen:'Karen Marsh: The latest.
你听,“Karen Marsh: 最新消息.
At her London Hotel today Miss Marsh told reporters she might retire.
今天在伦敦旅馆,Marsh小姐告诉记者她可能要退休.
She said she couldn't make up her mind.
她说她还拿不定主意.
She said she would have to ask her future husband.
她说她得问问她的未婚夫.
She said her future husband would not let her make another film.
她说她的未婚夫不会再让她拍电影.
Then she introduced us to Carlos and told us they would get married next week.'
然后她把我们介绍给Carlos,并告诉我们他们下星期结婚.”
That's sensational news,isn't it, Kate?
Kate,这真是条轰动的消息,不是吗?
It certainly is.
的确是.
He'll be her sixth husband!
他将是她的第6个丈夫!